From the darkness he will rise.
Shadow Master is a action, fantasy, thriller film
directed by Pearry Reginald Teo.
After being slain by a group of criminals, a man is reborn with animal-like
superpowers and makes it his mission to right the wrongs of his city.
An Voaen, played by D.Y. Sao.
Detective Russells, played by Layton Matthews.
Samael, played by Brian Le.
Boon-Nam, played by Craig Ng.
Dewitt, played by Anna Harr.
Janett, played by Luciana Faulhaber.
The Eminence in Shadow (Japanese: 陰の実力者になりたくて!, Hepburn: Kage no Jitsuryokusha ni Naritakute!) is
a Japanese light novel series written by Daisuke Aizawa and illustrated by Tōzai.
It began serialization online in May 2018 on the user-generated
novel publishing website Shōsetsuka ni Narō.
It was later acquired by Enterbrain, who have
published the series since November 2018.
A manga adaptation with art by Anri Sakano has been serialized in Kadokawa
Shoten's seinen manga magazine Comp Ace since December 2018.
A spin-off manga by Seta U, titled Kage no Jitsuryokusha ni Naritakute!
Shadow Gaiden (陰の実力者になりたくて！ しゃどーがいでん; "The Eminence in Shadow!
Shadow Side Story"), was also serialized via Comp
Ace from July 2019 to September 2023.
A second spin-off manga by Kanco, titled Kage no Jitsuryokusha ni Naritakute!
Master of Garden: Shichikage Retsuden (陰の実力者になりたくて！マスターオブガーデン～七陰列伝～; "The Eminence in Shadow: Master of
Garden – Seven Shadows Chronicles"), started serialization via Comic Walker in May 2024.
Both the light novel and main manga have been
licensed in North America by Yen Press.
An anime television series adaptation produced by Nexus
aired from October 2022 to February 2023.
A second season aired from October to December 2023.
An anime film, titled The Eminence in Shadow: Lost
Echoes, was announced in December 2023.
The film explores themes of martial arts, superhero, apocalypse, super power.
The tone is intense.